Guide to the George Harmon Coxe Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 1997 Acquisition, 1897-1980; 2; 20.14; (49 boxes)
  - Writings, 1931-1965
    - Key Witness, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated and corrected [Published in Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine?], 1958 (Box 37)
    - Killer's Nemesis, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Dime Detective], undated (Box 37)
    - Lady in Black, novel, typescript, carbon, annotated, revised draft, undated (Box 38)
    - The Lady is Afraid, chapter outline, typescript, corrected by the author, undated (Box 38)
    - The Lady is Afraid, character synopsis, typescript, original, corrected by the author, undated (Box 38)
    - The Lady is Afraid, outline, typescript, original, corrected by the author, undated (Box 38)
    - The Lady is Right, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 38)
    - Lady Killer, plot outline, typescript, annotated by the author., undated (Box 38)
    - Lady Killer, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in American Magazine?], undated (Box 38)
    - The Last Week, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 38)
    - The Last Witness, short story, typescript, annotated and corrected [Published in Detective Fiction Weekly?], undated (Box 38)
    - The Letter of Death, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 38)
    - Letters are Dangerous, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 38)
    - Mad Masquerade, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Clues?], undated (Box 38)
    - Marathons are Different, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in the Saturday Evening Post?], undated (Box 38)
    - Marathons are Different, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, revised draft [Published in The Saturday Evening Post?], undated (Box 38)
    - Margin Murder, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, and corrected [Published in Detective Story?], undated (Box 38)
    - Material Witness, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Detective Fiction Weekly?], undated (Box 38)
    - Midnight Madness, outline, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 38)
    - Mixed Drinks, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Black Mask?], undated (Box 38)
    - Moment of Violence, poem, typescript, original, 1961 (Box 38)
    - Moment of Violence, poem, typescript, carbon, annotated [Incomplete draft], undated (Box 38)
    - Murder by Schedule, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Clues?], 1934 July (Box 38)
    - Murder by Midnight, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 38)
    - Murder in Havana, short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 38)
    - Murder in Vain, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in All Detective?], 1934 August (Box 38)
    - Murder Mix-up, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 38)
    - Murder Street, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Dime Detective], undated (Box 38)
    - Murder Touch, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Detective Fiction Weekly?], 1935 October (Box 38)
    - Murder With Pictures, novel, Chapters 1-23, typescript, original, and carbon, with printer's corrections, undated; 4 (Box 39)
    - Musical Ability at College, essay, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 39)
    - My Thoughts, poem, typescript, original [2 copies], undated (Box 39)
    - New Electrical Circuit for High Speed Photography, essay, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 39)
    - No Hard Feelings, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in Colliers?], undated; 2 (Box 39)
    - No Loose Ends, short story, typescript, carbon, 1948 (Box 39)
    - No Loose Ends, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Liberty?], 1948 July (Box 39)
    - No Quarter, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Dime Magazine?], 1933 May (Box 39)
    - No Time to Kill, novel, Chapters 1-3, typescript, original, corrected, original draft. With: typescript letter signed to GHC from Carl Brandt, 1940 May 6 (Box 39)
    - No Time to Kill, novel, Chapters 4-8, typescript, original, corrected, original draft. With: typescript letter signed to GHC from Carl Brandt, 1940 May 13 (Box 39)
    - No Time to Kill, novel, Chapters 9-14, typescript, original, corrected, original draft. With: typescript letter signed to GHC from Carl Brandt, 1940 May 20 (Box 39)
    - No Time to Kill, novel, Chapters 15-22, typescript, original, corrected, original draft. With: typescript letter signed to GHC from Carl Brandt, 1940 May 27 (Box 39)
    - No Work No Pay, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Top Notch?], undated (Box 39)
    - Notes on "The Ghost", a television show for ABC, essay, typescript, carbon, annotated by the author, 1969 (Box 39)
    - On the Nostalgic Side, essay, typescript, original, annotated, and corrected by the author, undated (Box 39)
    - One for the Box, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Thrilling Detective?], 1934 (Box 39)
    - Overnight Guest, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in This Week?], undated (Box 39)
    - The Painted Nail, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated and corrected [Published in Liberty?], 1945 May 5 (Box 39)
    - Partners in Crime, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Colliers?], undated (Box 39)
    - Party Murder, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Detective Fiction Weekly?], 1934 (Box 39)
    - Percentage Plus, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Blue Book?], 1934 (Box 39)
    - The Perfect Frame, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Thrilling Detective?], undated (Box 39)
    - Peril Afloat, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Thrilling Detective?], 1936 November (Box 40)
    - Pinch Hitters, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in Black Mask?], undated (Box 40)
    - A Pitcher of Cider, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - Planned Luck, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, and corrected, undated (Box 40)
    - Portrait of Murder, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - A Present from Casey, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Black Mask?], [no year] April 15 (Box 40)
    - The Price of Malice, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - The Proper Incentive, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 40)
    - Protection Promised, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 40)
    - Psychology Stuff, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Thrilling Detective?], 1934 February (Box 40)
    - Push-Over, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in Black Mask?], undated (Box 40)
    - The Quiz Murders, outline, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - Reason Enough, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - The Rejection Boogey, essay, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - Reprisal, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, 1934 July (Box 40)
    - A Routine Check, short story, typescript carbon [Published in Ellery Queen?], 1958 (Box 40)
    - Routine Work, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - Schooled in Crime, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, 1934 (Box 40)
    - Secret Payment, short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 40)
    - The Shuttered Room, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in American Magazine?], undated (Box 40)
    - A Simple Market File, essay, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - Sleigh Ride, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Dime Detective?], undated (Box 40)
    - The Slip, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Phantom Detective?], 1934 March (Box 40)
    - So Right for Laura, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Colliers?], undated (Box 40)
    - Soft Assignment, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Detective Fiction Weekly?], 1934 November (Box 40)
    - A Solo for Sleepy, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Clues?], 1934 May (Box 40)
    - Someday I'll Tell Him, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - Someday I'll Tell Him, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in This Week?], undated (Box 40)
    - Some Have Illusions, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, and corrected [Published in Ainslee's?], 1935 January (Box 40)
    - Speak No Evil, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 40)
    - Special Assignment, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Black Mask?], undated (Box 41)
    - Special Delivery, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Top Notch?], undated (Box 41)
    - Special Messenger, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 41)
    - Starting That Mystery Book, essay, typescript, carbon [Published in the Winter?], undated (Box 41)
    - Stop Sign, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Top Notch?], undated (Box 41)
    - Stuffed Shirts, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, 1934 (Box 41)
    - Testimonial, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Argosy?], undated (Box 41)
    - Thanks for Everything, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Liberty?], undated (Box 41)
    - Touch System, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 41)
    - Train Dispatching by Remote Control, essay, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Popular Mechanics?], undated (Box 41)
    - Triple Exposure, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in American Magazine?], 1951 November (Box 41)
    - Trouble at Basatique, [Isle of New Fortunes], short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Blue Book?], 1935 (Box 41)
    - Trouble for Two, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 41)
    - Turn About, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 41)
    - The Twelfth Woman, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, 1934 (Box 41)
    - Two Man Job, short story, typescript, carbon [Published in Black Mask?], 1934 February 5 (Box 41)
    - Ungallant Evidence, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, 1935 (Box 41)
    - Venturous Lady, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 41)
    - The Weakest Link, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, and corrected, undated (Box 41)
    - Weapon of Fear, short story, typescript [Published in American Magazine?], undated (Box 41)
    - The Web of Death, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, 1934 January 27 (Box 41)
    - Weekend Pass, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in Colliers?], undated (Box 41)
    - The Widow Had a Gun, short story, typescript, carbon, annotated [Published in American Magazine?], undated (Box 41)
    - You Gotta Be Tough, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 41)
    - Notes concerning short stories autograph manuscript and typescript, 1931-1936; 2 (Box 42)
    - Miscellaneous notes, hologoraph. With: 4 clippings, undated, 1937 (Box 42)
    - Anniversary Present, short story, typescript, original, corrected, 1948 (Box 42)
    - Deadly Images, novel, typescript, original, corrected, with notes for the printer, 1964; 4 (Box 42)
    - Death at the Isthmus, notes, typescript, original, with annotations. With: a letter to Carl [Brandt?] from Robert Meskill, 1953 October 12 (Box 42)
    - The Doctor Makes it Murder, short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 42)
    - The Lady is Right, short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 43)
    - The Lady is Right, short story, typescript, carbon, revised draft, undated (Box 43)
    - Letter to a Widow, notes, autograph manuscript, and typescript original, with annotations, undated (Box 43)
    - Manuscripts and their Travels, autograph manuscript, bound, circa 1931 (Box 43)
    - Mystery Telephone Show, story outline, typescript, original, corrected, and original, carbon, 1948 May 10 (Box 43)
    - [No Way to Kill], notes, typescript, original, corrected, undated; 4 (Box 43)
    - No Way to Kill, novel, typescript, carbon. 4 folders, undated; 4 (Box 43)
    - Notes on "Crime Lab" and Lt. Steve Masters, essay, typescript, carbon, 1951 February 14 (Box 43)
    - Some Additional Thoughts on Dr. Standish, essay, typescript, carbon, corrected, signed, 1951 June 18 (Box 43)
    - A Suggestion for CBS, essay, typescript, original, undated (Box 43)
    - A Suggestion for NBC, essay, typescript, carbon [2 copies], 1949 May 19 (Box 43)
    - A Suggestion for a New Radio Show, essay, typescript, carbon, and typescript, carbon, correct [2 copies], 1949 February 8 (Box 43)
    - The Unfair Question, essay, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 43)
    - An Easy Way to Go, undated; 3 (Box 44)
    - The Candid Imposter, undated; 5 (Box 44)
    - Double Identity, undated; 6 (Box 44)
    - Fenner, undated; 4 (Box 45)
    - Cosmopolitan magazine, Man in the Middle, 1963, undated (Box 45)
    - Character sketches, plot outlines [?]
      - One Hour to Kill, undated; 3 (Box 45)
      - The Reluctant Heiress, undated; 3 (Box 45)
      - The Ring of Truth, 1965; 3 (Box 46)
      - Woman with a Gun, undated; 3 (Box 46)
      - The Big Gamble, 1958 (Box 46)
      - Deadly Image, undated (Box 46)
      - Double Identity, undated (Box 46)
      - Error of Judgement, undated (Box 46)
      - Eye Witness, 1951 (Box 46)
      - The Frightened Fiancee, undated (Box 46)
      - The Impetuous Mistress, undated (Box 46)
      - Moment of Violence, undated (Box 46)
      - One Hour to Kill, 1963 (Box 46)
      - One Minute Past Eight, undated (Box 46)
      - One Way Out, undated (Box 46)
      - The Shuttered Room, undated (Box 46)
      - Slack Tide, undated (Box 46)
      - The Widow Had a Gun, undated (Box 46)
      - Man on a Rope, undated (Box 46)
      - Murder on their Minds, undated (Box 46)
    - [Coxe, George Harmon?] Untitled essay, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 47)
    - Fragments, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 47)
    - Notes, miscellaneous, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 47)
    - Notes, miscellaneous, autograph manuscript and typescript, 1931, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled essay, typescript, original, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character outlines and notes, autograph manuscript, and typescript, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character outline and notes, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, plot outline, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, plot outline, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, chapter outlines, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character synopsis, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character synopsis, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, chapter outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, plot outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, with autograph manuscript notes, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, chapter outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character outlines, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, chapter outline, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, chapter outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, character outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, chapter outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novel, Chapters 1-21, typescript, carbon, corrected [p. 1-3 missing], undated; 3 (Box 47)
    - Untitled novelette, plot outline, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novelette, character outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled novelette, plot outline, typescript, carbon, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled serial, chapter outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled serial, character outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled serial, character outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled serial, plot outline, typescript, original, annotated by the author, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled serial, character outline, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 47)
    - Untitled serial, plot outline, typescript, original, with corrections by the author. With: typescript letter signed to GHC from Carl Brandt, 1941 December 4 (Box 47)
    - Untitled serial, plot outline, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 47)
  - Writings of Others, 1943-1967
    - Barkham, John. "Among Books and Authors," article published in the Saturday Review, typescript, electrostat copy, 1965 August 21 (Box 48)
    - Cole, Alonzo Dean. "The Adventures of Jack Casy, Press Photographer: #93 ... Free Confession," radio script, of a short story by George Harmon Coxe, typescript, mimeograph, annotated, 1945 May 8 (Box 48)
    - Cole, Alonzo Dean. Blind Justice, script, typescript, mimeograph, corrected, 1948; 2 (Box 48)
    - Cole, Alonzo Dean. "Crime Photographer #153 ... 'Twas the Day After Christmas or Buried Evidence," radio script of a short story by George Harmon Coxe, typescript, mimeograph, annotated, 1946 December 26 (Box 48)
    - Cole, Alonzo Dean. "Murder for Breakfast," radio script of a short story by George Harmon Coxe, typescript, mimeograph, 1943 September 30 (Box 48)
    - [Frazer, Jan?] "Coxe - Woman with a Gun," script, typescript, electrostat copy, corrected, annotated, undated (Box 48)
    - Hackaday, Hal C. "It's a Mystery to Me," radio script, typescript, mimeograph, corrected, 1950 November 5 (Box 48)
    - Holt, Felix. "Death Certificate," a television treatment of a short story by George Harmon Coxe, typescript, original, 1943 September 30 (Box 48)
    - Holt, Felix. "Dr. Paul Standisll - Medical Examiner," television adaptation script, typescript, carbon. With: typescript letter signed to GHC from Peggy Smith, 1950 May 29 (Box 48)
    - Holt, Felix. "Dr. Paul Standisll - Medical Examiner," television adaptation script, typescript, carbon. With: typescript letter signed to GHC from Francis Head, 1950 July 21 (Box 48)
    - Hord, Frank T. Excerpt from a lecture, typescript, original, undated (Box 48)
    - Houts, Marshall. Where Death Delights, unrevised, uncorrected proofs, 1967 (Box 48)
    - James, Raymond [Alias the Dead?], play, typescript, original, corrected. With: stage sketches, undated; 4 (Box 48)
    - Knight, Alma. "Double Trouble for a Crime," a television treatment of a short story by George Harmon Coxe, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 48)
    - Ruscoll, Joseph. "Double Negative," television treatment of a short story by George Harmon Coxe, typescript, mimeograph, annotated by GHC, undated (Box 48)
    - Schweitzer, Gertrude. "Hit and Run," script, typescript, mimeograph, revised draft, 1956 October 17 (Box 48)
    - Unidentified author [George Harmon Coxe], speech, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 48)
    - Unidentified author. "The Eagle's Brood," Columbia Broadcasting Company, script, typescript, mimeograph, 1947 March 5 (Box 48)
    - Unidentified author. "Hyde Hall Brochure," typescript, electrostat copy, undated (Box 48)
    - Unidentified author. Air Features, Inc. Presents "Crime Photographer", report, mimeograph, 1954 (Box 48)
    - Unidentified author. Warren Hull Show, script, typescript, mimeograph, annotated, 1950 (Box 48)
  - Correspondence, 1897-1980
    - Unidentified, 1941-1980, undated (Box 49)
    - Unidentified, 1971-1977 (Box 49)
    - A-B, 1963-1981 (Box 49)
    - A, 1922-1980, undated (Box 49)
    - Ba-Be, 1942-75, undated (Box 49)
    - Bl-Bz, 1941-79 (Box 49)
    - C, 1921-1977 (Box 49)
    - C, 1940-1980 (Box 49)
    - D-G, 1924-1981 (Box 49)
    - D, 1922-1980, undated (Box 49)
    - E, 1942-1970 (Box 49)
    - Fa-Fi, 1942-1980 (Box 49)
    - Fj-Fz, 1962-1980 (Box 49)
    - G, 1942-1975 (Box 49)
    - H-K, 1949-1981 (Box 49)
    - Ha-He, 1942-1976 (Box 50)
    - Hf-Hz, 1938-1968 (Box 50)
    - I, 1938-1968 (Box 50)
    - J, 1950-1966 (Box 50)
    - K, 1953-1979, undated (Box 50)
    - L, 1922-1979, undated (Box 50)
    - Ma-Md, 1942-1979 (Box 50)
    - Me-Mz, 1942-1980 (Box 50)
    - N-P, 1951-1977 (Box 50)
    - N, 1942-1976 (Box 50)
    - O, 1957-1976 (Box 50)
    - P, 1923-1980 (Box 50)
    - Q-Z, 1949-1981 (Box 50)
    - Q, undated (Box 50)
    - R, 1922-1980, undated (Box 50)
    - Sa-Sc, 1942-1972 (Box 50)
    - Se, 1963-1975 (Box 50)
    - Sf-Sz, 1942-1976 (Box 50)
    - T, 1942-1980 (Box 51)
    - U, 1942-1974 (Box 51)
    - V, 1950, undated (Box 51)
    - Wa-Wh, 1942-1976 (Box 51)
    - Wi-Wz, 1942-1975 (Box 51)
    - X-Z, 1943-1980 (Box 51)
    - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1941-1976; 22 (Box 52)
    - Automobile Mutual Insurance Company of America, 1961-1970 (Box 52)
    - Barclay's Bank Limited, 1955-1980 (Box 52)
    - Blassingame, Lurton, 1931-1932; 2 (Box 52)
    - Brandt & Brandt, 1940-1969; 18 (Box 53)
    - Brandt & Brandt, 1970-1980; 10 (Box 54)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1942-1953 (Box 55)
    - Cornell University
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1976 (Box 55)
      - Cornell Club of New York, 1953-1976 (Box 55)
      - Cornell Football, 1962-1964 (Box 55)
      - Cornell University Library, 1960-1979 (Box 55)
      - Department of Physical Education and Athletics, 1960-1975 (Box 55)
      - Office of Estate Affairs, 1969-1976 (Box 55)
      - Office of the President, 1972-1975 (Box 55)
      - Office of University Counsel and Secretary of the Corporation, 1970-1972 (Box 55)
      - Office of University Development, 1950-1980 (Box 55)
      - The Tower Club, 1972-1980 (Box 55)
      - Trust Office, 1972-1980 (Box 55)
    - Coxe, Elizabeth, 1952-1953, undated (Box 55)
    - Coxe, Janet, 1940-1953, undated (Box 55)
    - Coxe, Mrs. George Harmon, Sr., 1953-1966, undated; 2 (Box 55)
    - Coxe, George Harmon, III, undated (Box 55)
    - Mystery Writers of America, Inc., 1950-1975 (Box 55)
    - Nebel, Dorothy, 1967, undated (Box 55)
    - Nebel, Louis Frederick, 1950-1966, undated (Box 55)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy - Davis Library, 1953-1979 (Box 55)
    - Pryor, Laurence, 1960-1969 (Box 55)
    - Sanders and Conroy, 1940-1950 (Box 55)
    - Thomas Cook and Son, Inc., 1957-1958; 2 (Box 55)
    - Unidentified, 1924 (Box 55)
    - Walsh, Tom, 1949-1972, undated; 2 (Box 55)
    - Correspondence of others
      - Brandt & Brandt, 1942 (Box 55)
      - Coxe, Elizabeth, 1971-1980 (Box 55)
      - Coxe, Harriet, 1897-1922 (Box 55)
    - Financial papers, 1922-1975 (Box 56)
    - A.M. Heath & Co., Ltd, 1972-1982 (Box 56)
    - Agenzia Letteria Internazionale, 1958-1961 (Box 56)
    - Arnoldo Mondadori Editore, 1956-1974 (Box 56)
    - Barclays Bank Limited, 1966-1983 (Box 56)
    - Brandt & Brandt, 1948-1981; 5 (Box 56)
    - Columbia Broadcasting Company, 1949, undated (Box 56)
    - Gennossenschaftliche Zentral bank AG Librarie Artheme Fayard, 1966-1982; 2 (Box 56)
    - Robert Hale & Company, 1969-1974 (Box 56)
    - Utig. Mij. De Combinatie, 1966 (Box 56)